Guide to the Judith Braun Papers MSS.530
Fales Library and Special Collections
Judith Braun Papers
1978-2014
Fales Library and Special Collections
Braun, Judith
MSS.530
6.5 Linear Feet in 4 record cartons, 1 manuscript box, and 2 oversize flat boxes.
The Judith Braun Papers consist of records of artist Judith Braun's creative feminist work from 1987 to 2014. Artwork, research, correspondence, and articles pertaining to her exhibitions from 1978 to 1997 create the bulk of this collection. After graduating from Empire State College in Albany, New York in 1979 with a Bachelor's Degree in Fine Arts, Braun pursued realistic figure painting until 1982 when she transitioned to combining her visual artwork with text and innuendo through photocopying. The artwork within this collection reflects Braun's changing artistic output and her creation of the persona Weinperson. Applications for grants, residencies, and show proposals from 1987 to 2011 are included as a part of this collection as well as a small amount of interviews from 2012 to 2014. The posters available in this collection are remnants of Braun's large scale photocopying process.
Scope and Contents
The Judith Braun Papers consist of records of artist Judith Braun's creative work from 1987 to 2014. Artwork, research, correspondence, and articles pertaining to exhibitions of her work from 1978 to 1997 create the bulk of this collection. The collection also contains applications for grants, residencies, and show proposals from 1987 to 2011, as well as interviews with Braun from 2012 to 2014. Of particular significance to the trajectory of Braun's artistic career are the collection of tarot card readings from 1998 to 2001, which inspired her to re-enter the art world in 2001. The collection documents Braun's large scale photocopying process with initial images, enlarged photocopied grid pieces, photographs and slides of large scale wall hangings, and large scale posters.
Biographical Note
Judith Braun (1947 - ), also known as Judith Weinperson and Weinperson, is a New York City-based artist. After graduating from Empire State College in Albany, New York, in 1979 with a Bachelor's Degree in Fine Arts, she pursued realistic figure painting until 1982 when she transitioned to combining her visual artwork with text and innuendo through photocopying. During this artistic transition Braun was pursuing her Masters in Arts and Masters in Fine Arts at State University of New York at Albany, New York, graduating in 1983. In 1989 she created the persona Weinperson, an alteration of her married name Weinman. The Weinperson persona represented Braun in her experiments with racial and sexual innuendos in her photocopied creations. Braun exhibited as Weinperson or Judith Weinperson from 1988 to 1995 before retreating from her creative practice until 2003.
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are open without restrictions.
Arrangement
This collection has not been arranged by an archivist. The materials are arranged in the order in which they were received from the donor Judith Braun. The donor arrangement has ten series without subseries. These series were labeled by the artist to aid her artistic process. The series arrangement is:
Series I. Proposals - Correspondence - Shows
Series II. Articles - Reading
Series III. Applications
Series IV. Artwork
Series V. Early Brochures
Series VI. Notebooks
Series VII. Newspaper Clippings
Series VIII. Weinperson
Series IX. Tarot
Series X. Posters
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Donated by Judith Braun, 2017. The accession number associated with this gift is 2018.029.
Feminism and art -- New York (State) -- New York.; Art -- Exhibitions -- New York (State) -- New York.; Race in art.; Connotation (Linguistics).; Art -- New York (State) -- New York.; Sex and art.
- Series I. Proposals - Correspondence - Shows, 1987-2014
  Scope and Contents
  The Proposals - Correspondence - Shows series contains correspondence between Braun and organizations interested in her artwork and dates between 1987 to 2014. These organizations include jurored shows; non-profit galleries such as White Columns in New York, New York; and art institutions including The New Museum of Contemporary Art in New York, New York and Kunstlerhaus Bethanien in Berlin, Germany.
  - Letters - Galleries, 1987-1993 (Box 1, Folder 1-2)
  - A/C Project, Undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Alternative Museum, 1988-1991 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - American Fineart CO. Colin Deland, 1988-1991 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Arena - Show Papers, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Arena - Press Release, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Art in General, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - "ART MALL" New Museum, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Bad Girls, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Book Proposal - '93, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Cindy Nemser Ms. Magazine, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - C-LINE Grant Proposal, Undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Codex - Statement, Undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Codex- - Image "O.W.C.D.S.E.', 1993 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Columbia - SIX GOOD CASES FOR MANSLAUGHTER, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Conservation Info, 1989-1991 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Contacts/Proofs 1993, 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Cover Magazine, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Drawing Center, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Exquisite Corpse Drawing Center, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - FAWBUSH, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - FEATURE, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - "GETTING TO KNOW YOU" '92 Berlin, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Gregory Volk, Undated (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Grey Gallery 998-6780, 1988-1991 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Group Material, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - HE'S GOOD IN BED, Undated (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Hyde, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Interviews, 2012-2014 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Jagendorf Bacchi, Undated (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Kim Levin, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Kunsthalle, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Leipzig, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Letters to Editors, 1991-2005 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - LIST Kathy Holbreidt + Dana Friis Hausen, 1987-1989 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Marymount, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - New Museum - Proposals + Outreach, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Nurture Art, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - ON THE WALL, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Original Sin, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - OVERT EXPOSURE, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Pat Hearn - PHONE ART Proposal, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Phone - Art, Undated (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Pierogi Flat Files, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - PRATT, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Printed Matter Sex Machine, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - "PROMOTIONAL COPY" - 1993 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - PS 122, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - RECO Letters, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - RENT - A - FRIEND, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Rice Gallery - "BEYOND BROADSIDE" 1993 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Salon 94 - Jeanne Greenburg Rohatyn, 2011 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - SHARP - Grant Proposal, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Shoshana Wayne, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Soup Magazine, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Sonyun Yi - Solo Show 1990 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - STUX, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Valie Export, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - White Columns Solo White Room, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - White Columns - Benefit Auction 1992 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - White Columns Benefit 1993 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - White Columns Benefit 94, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 63)
- Series II. Articles - Reading, 1978-1997
  The Articles - Reading series includes clippings collected by Braun from 1978 to 1997 that influenced her artwork on racial and sexual innuendo. Publications include The Village Voice, The New York Times, and The New Yorker.
  - Art- Politics, 1985-1996 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Art - Pop/POMO, 1990-1992 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Bi-Racial Reports, 1990-1997 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Bio/Social Construction, 1993-1997 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - (Books) Feminist, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Books, 1991-1994 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Creative Thinking, 1978-1995 (Box 1, Folder 70 - 71)
  - Problem Solving, Undated (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Criticism (Critics), 1982-1994 (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Domestic Violence Fact Sheet, Undated (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Drug Therapy (Psychedelics), 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - Art-Feminism, 1980-1991 (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - Germany, 1992-1995 (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - Global/Cultures, 1990-1994 (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - Hi-Tech, 1993-1995 (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - Humor, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - Identity/Persona, 1987-1994 (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - Language, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - Lesbian/Bisex, 1990-1992 (Box 1, Folder 83)
  - Men's Issues, 1992-1995 (Box 1, Folder 84)
  - Moral Issues, 1990-1995 (Box 1, Folder 85)
  - People, 1990-1997 (Box 1, Folder 86)
  - Performance, 1989-1994 (Box 1, Folder 87)
  - Porn, 1993-1993 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Radical, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Psychology, 1992-1996 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - (Race) Film/TV, 1992-1995 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - (Race) Issues/Commentary, 1992-1997 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - (Race) Multi Racial, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Music, 1990-1996 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - (Race) People/Commentary, 1993-1996 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Rape, Undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Sex, 1990-1992 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Sexism, 1990-1994 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - PC/Speech, 1989-1993 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Style, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Thinking, Undated (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Victim, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Welfare, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - (Women) Aging, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - (Women) Film/Theatre, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - (Women) Rights, 1993-1995 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - (Women) Violence, 1992-1994 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Series III. Applications, 1988-2003
  The Applications series contains correspondence between Braun and organizations providing grant and residencies, dating between 1988 and 2003.
  - New York Foundation for the Arts Grants 1988 - 89 painting sculpture, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - National Endowment for the Arts - 1991 - 92, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - New York Foundation for the Arts - OCT. 92 94, 1992-1994 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - National Endowment for the Arts - 1995 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - New York Foundation for the Arts Video 2003 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Rome Prize, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Art Residencies Info, 2000-2001 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Mailing Lists, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Series IV. Artwork, 1992-1994
  The Artwork series is a record of Braun's creative process producing her 152 week serial art piece ANNOUNCEMENT and her colossal photocopied wall art. The photocopied images in this series are the the inspiration for her innuendo artwork in between 1992 and 1994.
  - AMAZING GRACE, Undated (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - ABOUT READY, Undated (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - ASKING FOR IT, Undated (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - BAD, Undated (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - BAOBAB TREE, Undated (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - BLACK-EYE BLUES, Undated (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - "BLIND PIANO PLAYER", Undated (Box 2, Folder 35-37)
  - BLUE PENIS - New, Undated (Box 2, Folder 38-39)
  - BURNING BUSH, Undated (Box 2, Folder 40-42)
  - CAN DO, Undated (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - CAN SEE, Undated (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - CAN'T WAIT, Undated (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Cards - ''JUST SHUT UP", Undated (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - CARD - R.M.P., Undated (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - CONDOMS, Undated (Box 2, Folder 48-49)
  - COVENANT WOMAN, Undated (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - DA POOR, Undated (Box 2, Folder 51 - 52)
  - EATING MY CAKE, Undated (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - EXPLOSIONS, Undated (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - FEELS FINE, Undated (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - FELT UP, Undated (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - FIREMAN, Undated (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Frames - FUCKIN CONDOMS, Undated (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - "FUCK THIS SHIT", Undated (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - GETS AWAY, Undated (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - G.U.L.P. - #08-10-92 "LOOK OUT" - Blk/Pink, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - HANGING, Undated (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - HAS EARS, Undated (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - HENRY + SYLVIA, Undated (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - HOW TO: Original, Undated (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - HOW TO: Second Version, Undated (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - "I THINK I LOVE YOU", Undated (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - "JUST EAT IT", Undated (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - KNOWS WHAT, Undated (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - PUSSY - R.M.P., Undated (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - PUSSY #1, Undated (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - PUSSY, Undated (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - READ MY PUSSY - Rag Paper Blue/Blk., Undated (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - red mi poose - White Columns Piece, Undated (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - READ MY PUSSY - Acetates, Undated (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - READ MY PUSSY - Faces, Undated (Box 2, Folder 76-77)
  - READ MY PUSSY - Small Mouth Grid Edition, Undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - READ MY PUSSY - Small Diag. Edition, Undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - READ MY PUSSY Install Instructions, Undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - RED HOT BLUES, Undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - "SACRED ORDER" - Small Framed, Undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - SAYS SO, Undated (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - "SEEING STARS", Undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - SEX MANIAC - Buttons, Undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - SHOWS EM, Undated (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - "SKIN OF HER TEAT" - MISC., Undated (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - SO FUCK YOU, Undated (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - S.O.O.T.B.B. (FIREMAN), Undated (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - STANDS UP, Undated (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - "THE FOREST", Undated (Box 3, Folder 14-15)
  - "TIT ATTACKS", Undated (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - TOKEN OF MY lOVE, Undated (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - TOKENS OF MY LOVE, Undated (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - "WEINPERSON WANTS YOU", Undated (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Breasts, Undated (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Circles concentric, Undated (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Face on Glass - "SEE STARS" 6 cases, Undated (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Fire, Undated (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Guns, Undated (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Half-Tones, Undated (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Hands, Undated (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - James Brown, Undated (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Lips, Undated (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Me, Undated (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Meadow, Undated (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Moisture, Undated (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Notebook Stuff, Undated (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Paintings - Single Standard MEEK FEET Restoration, Undated (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Painting - HANGING ANGEL, Undated (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Paintings: Portrait of Angel Landscapes, Undated (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Paul + House, Undated (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Paul + Me, Undated (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - PUSSY - PROUD, Undated (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - PUSSY: WILD, Undated (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Rosa Parks, Undated (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - "SO... I HAVE DIFFICULTY", Undated (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Unfucking Titled, Undated (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - RACE xeroxes, Undated (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Ray Charles, Undated (Box 3, Folder 44)
- Series V. Early Brochures, 1980-1994
  The Early Brochures series consists of pamphlets from Braun's exhibitions from 1980 to 1992 in both solo and group shows.
  - Early Brochures, 1980-1994 (Box 3, Folder 45 - 51)
- Series VI. Notebooks, 1978-1994
  The Notebooks series contains notebooks describing Braun's compositions from 1978 to 1994. Included in this series are clippings collected by Braun to influence her artwork on racial and sexual innuendo as well as slides of her work from 1978 to 1994. Braun's handwritten notebooks contain few sketches and are filled with lists and art production goals. These notebooks document the art creation of a year or are dedicated to a specific art piece.
  - 6 November 1993 - 12 December 1994, 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - 9 December 1992- 5 November 1993, 1992-1993 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Berlin - Show 1992 Preshow Notes (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - 2 April 1991 - 7 August 1991 (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - 30 July 1990 - 2 April 1991, 1990-1992 (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - 31 March 1989 - 25 July 1990, 1989-1990 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - 3 June 1988 - 31 March 1989, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - 4 August 1987 - 30 May 1988, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - 6 May 1987 - 30 July 1987 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - 6 January 1986 - 6 May 1987, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Painting 6 January 1985 - 17 December 1985 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - 1979 - 80 - SUNYA (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - The State Wall 1979 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Pierce Hall Mural 1978 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Empire State College 1ST Contract - Bill Frankonis Readings, Undated (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Announcement Cards 1980's - 90's, 1982-1994 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Series VII. Newspaper Clippings, 1978-1994
  The Newspaper Clippings series contains articles taken from publications, from 1978 to 1994, such as The Village Voice, The New York Times, and The New Yorker.
  - Early Newspaper Clippings, 1978-1987 (Box 4, Folder 12-14)
  - Xerox Press, 1982-1994 (Box 4, Folder 15-17)
  - Xerox Slides, 1981-1994 (Box 4, Folder 18-20)
  - Slides, 1978-1997 (Box 4, Folder 21-22)
- Series VIII. Weinperson, 1993-2001
  The Weinperson series consists of a numerical series of photocopied postcards and production material for the art piece ANNOUNCEMENT. This material dates from 1993 to 2001 and was created by Braun using her Weinperson persona exploring her visual interpretations of racial and sexual innuendo. The finished product of 152 post cards are arranged together at the beginning of the series and then the preparation for each week's art piece is collected in numbered folders.
  - Weinperson ANNOUNCEMENT, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - YES, I HAVE NO RESERVATIONS, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - ANNOUNCEMENTS Mailing List/Stamps, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - ANNOUNCEMENTS - "MIDDLE-AGE-SEX-MANIAC" #1, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - #2 ANNOUNCEMENTS - "MORE FUCKING TIME", 1993 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - ANNOUNCEMENTS - "TOO" #3, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - ANNOUNCEMENTS - "GOOD SECRET" #4, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - ANNOUNCEMENTS - "BORN-ON-A-BACK-SEAT" #5, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - ANNOUNCEMENTS "I WANT TO DANCE W/YOU" #6, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - ANNOUNCEMENTS "AND SHOUT NOW" #7, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - "MORALITY FROM DEVIANCE" 8, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - "LOUDER NOW" #9, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - "NICE & DIRTY #10, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - "WEINPERSONALLY YOURS" #11, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - "JUST FUCKING WITH YOU" #12, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - "I'M NOT JUST FUCKING W/YOU" #13, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - "YOU CAN CALL ME WEINBABE" #14, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - "... OR YOU CAN CALL ME ROSA PARKS" #15, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - "I COULD CARE MORE OR LESS" #16, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - "ONLY 1/2 BAD" #17, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - "JUST 12 HOURS A DAY" #18, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - "OR BY APPOINTMENT" #19, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - #20 "IF I CAN SQUEEZE YOU IN", 1993 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - #21 "BOY, I'D LOVE TO SEE YOU IN THIS", 1993 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - #22 "WITH MORE THAN ONE" - JULY 2'93, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - "NOT JUST PLAIN MORE" - JULY 9-93 23, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - MORE THAN EVER 24, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - "BORN TO CHEETAH" - JULY 23 1993 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - UH-OH JULY, 30, 1993 26 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - BRAND NEW SECRET 27, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - "SECRET INTELLEGENCE 28, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - JUST READ BETWEEN MY SHEETS 29, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - I'M A REAL SMART ASS 30, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - "GETTING MY KICKS" 31, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - "YOU COULD MAKE ME CRY" 32, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - "OR WE COULD DO SOMETHING ELSE" 33, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - "SOME - YES I LOVE YOU I THING ELSE?" 34, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - "I'M THINKING... I'M THINKING 35, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - "BRAINSTORM" 36, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - "SO TWO HEADS ARE BETTER THAN ONE" 37, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - "FOR BETTER OR WORSE" #38, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - "I AM NOT SORRY THAT I FEEL GOOD EVEN" 39, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - "LOVE TO GET FELT-UP" 40, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - I WOULD LOVE RAY TO FIND ME ON HIS MIND 41, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - HOW TO HANDLE WET PUSSY 42, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - HOW I WANT TO MAKE PUSSY BEG 43, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - HOW I WANT TO FAKE IT 44, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - "REAL SWELL" 45, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - HOTEL 46, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - YES I HAVE NO RESERVATIONS 47, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - 1994, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - "GOOD JEANS" 49, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - JAN 14 1994 "CREDIT" 50 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - "I GOT A LICKIN COMIN" 51, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - "ONE YEAR SENTENCE" JAN 28 - 94 52, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 27)
- Series IX. Tarot, 1998-2001
  The Tarot series consists of tarot card readings and information on tarot interpretation, dating from 1998 to 2001.
  - Tarot School, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Daily Reads, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Theory Tarot, Undated (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Tarot Tarot - Me 1998 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Tarot - Me 1998 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Tarot - Me 1999 - 2001 (Box 5, Folder 33)
- Series X. Posters, 1990-1995
  The Posters series contains gridwork that was integral to Braun's colossal wall art photocopying process. This art process material is from her exhibitions in between 1990 and 1995. This collection contains gridwork posters from her exhibitions at Sonyun Yi Gallery in New York from 1990; the University of Alabama in Tuscaloosa, Alabama from 1991; On The Wall Gallery in New York from 1990; Columbia University in New York from 1991; the Drawing Center in New York from 1990; the Künstlerhaus Bethanien in Berlin, Germany from 1992; and the New Museum for Contemporary Art in New York in 1994.
  - READ MY PUSSY, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 1-2)
  - READ MY PUSSY - Village Voice, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - WEINPERSON, Undated (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - SACRED ORDER OF THE BURNING BUSH, Undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - 4.95, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - GOOD IN BED, Undated (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - SIX GOOD REASONS FOR MANSLAUGHTER, Undated (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - HAPPY BITCH SERIES, Undated (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - I THINK I LOVE YOU, Undated (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - THE BAOBAB TREE, Undated (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - JUST EAT IT, Undated (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - READ MY PUSSY, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Bad Girls Show, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - SACRED ORDER OF THE BURNING BUSH, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 3)